wavelifesciences.com 2018-01-15

# Privacy Policy | Wave Life Sciences

Effective November 9, 2015

This website is owned and operated by Wave Life Sciences Ltd. (“Company,” “we,” “our,” or “us”). This Privacy Policy describes the type of information we collect from visitors to our website, how we may use the information, and how we share it. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by the Company directly through this website and does not describe or apply to ways in which we may collect and use information obtained offline or through other sources, or the collection, use or disclosure policies or practices of any third party.

**Information Collection and Use**

The Company respects the privacy of visitors to our website. You may visit our website without telling us anything about yourself. If you choose to contact us and provide personally identifiable information, we will use it for the purpose for which you submitted it to us – for example, to respond to a request for information, or to apply for an open position with the Company.

We do not collect or maintain personally identifiable information for marketing, advertising or resale purposes, and will not share your personally identifiable information with ay other company or organization, except to the extent that any sharing is required for the provision of services as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not wish to receive any email or other communication from us after you request information, please contact use at [unsubscribe@wavelifesci.com](mailto:unsubscribe@wavelifesci.com).

**Cookies**

This website may use persistent and session “cookies,” which are small files that the website places on your computer for future identification purposes. These files are used for website customization the next time you visit our website. Cookies do not contain or transmit any personally identifiable information from your computer to our website. Your web browser may allow you to disable cookies, but some features on our website may not fully function if cookies are disabled.

**Transfer of Information**

We do not share personally identifiable information with other parties except as described in this Privacy Policy.

_Service Providers_ – We may engage third parties to host this website or provide other services to us that may involve your personally identifiable information, such as email marketing services. In such cases, we require service providers to maintain your personally identifiable information as confidential and to use the information only to perform the services specified by us in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy.

_Legal Process_ – We may release your personally identifiable information in response to a court order, subpoena, search warrant, or as required by applicable law or regulation.

_Other_ – We may access or disclose information, including personally identifiable information, to: (a) protect or defend our interests and the legal rights or property of the Company; (b) protect the rights, interest and safety and security or our website or members of the public; (c) protect against fraud. In addition, if we sell all or substantially all of the Company or sell or transfer all or a material part of our assets, or are otherwise involved in a merger or transfer or all or a material part of our business, we may transfer all information we have collected and stored, including your personally identifiable information, to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.

**Security**

The Company makes reasonable efforts to protect the personally identifiable information collected through its website when stored in the Company’s databases. However, we cannot guarantee that our website is 100% from tampering or “hacking.” Any data transmitted over the Internet can be at risk. PLEASE DO NOT SEND SENSITIVE PERSONAL HEALTH INFORMATION TO THE COMPANY VIA THE WEBSITE OR THE INTERNET.

**California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 entitles California residents to request information concerning whether a business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. As we have stated in this Privacy Policy, we will not sell or share your personal information anyone for their direct marketing purposes. California individuals who wish to request further information about our compliance with this law may contact us as specific in the “For Additional Information” section below.

**Do Not Track Notice  **

The Company does not track its users over time and across third party websites and therefore does not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals. No third party advertisements are permitted on the website.

**Links to Third Party Websites**

As a convenience to our visitors, this website may contain links to other websites that we believe may offer useful information. Those links are beyond our control and the policies and procedures of those websites govern your use of those sites. We have not reviewed and make no representations about the accuracy of information on third party websites and your linking to such websites is at your own risk.

**Data Transfers**

We may transfer the personally identifiable information we collect about you to countries other than the country in which the information originally was collected, including the United States. By submitting your personally identifiable information to this website, you unambiguously consent to such a transfer of your personally identifiable information.

**Privacy Policy Updates**

The Company may, at any time, revise this Privacy Policy by posting an update. You should consult the effective date at the top of this Privacy Policy. We will continue to use and/or disclose information in accordance with the policy in effect at the time the data was collected.

**For Additional Information**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices of this website, please contact [postmaster@wavelifesci.com](mailto:postmaster@wavelifesci.com).

You may also write us at:

WAVE Life Sciences USA  
733 Concord Avenue  
Cambridge, MA 02138
